Hi, welcome to session fourteen,
嗨，欢迎来到第十四节课，
we're going to talk about giving your playing some style,
我们将讨论如何赋予你的演奏风格，
we're going to talk about the little nuances, that we can add to our playing,
我们将讨论我们可以在演奏中加入的细微差别，
that's going to give it some style,
这将给我们的演奏带来一些风格，
give it some uniqueness,
赋予它一些独特性，
become our own voice.
成为我们自己的声音。
Some of those techniques are bends,
其中一些技巧是推弦，
we're going to learn the proper technique for bending,
我们将学习适当的推弦技术，
we're going to talk about slides,
我们将谈论滑弦，
talk about hammer-ons and pull-offs,
讨论击弦和勾弦，
as well as palm muting with our hand,
以及用我们的手做手掌闷音，
[] going about doing octaves, like we would in Jazz work.
我们将讨论八度，在爵士乐作品中。
In our guitar tips section, we're going to talk about using a capo,
在吉他技巧部分，我们将讨论如何使用变调夹，
as well as using harmonics
以及如何使用泛音，
and incorporating them into our playing.
并将它们整合到我们的弹奏中。
So we've got a lot to do so,
所以我们还有很多事情要做，
let's go ahead and get started.
所以让我们继续并开始吧。
Okay, today we're gonna talk about giving your playing some style,
好的，今天我们将讨论给你的演奏一些风格，
these, these are the little nuance things,
这些是细微差别，
that add creative, you're your own voice to your music,
增加创造力，在你的音乐中你自己的声音，
okay, so you don't sound like just everybody else around
好的，所以你听起来不像周围的其他人，
and there's several different,
有几个不同的，
I just listed a few of them,
我只列出了几个，
we're going to talk about them
我们将讨论它们，
and go through the proper technique form all these different things.
并通过适当的技术形成所有这些不同的东西。
First thing, we're going to start off with and one of the easiest is sliding to notes,
首先，我们要开始做的事情是滑动音符，
man I was it was a long, one of the first things I've discovered,
这是我发现的第一个东西，
that if you slide up to a note, it kind of sounds cool,
如果你滑到一个音符，它听起来有点酷，
so let's practice that,
所以让我们练习一下，
sliding just involves you tap whatever note you're going for,
滑弦包括你敲击任何你想要的音符，
let's say I'm going for this fifth string,
假设我要弹第五弦，
or fifth fret second string E,
或者第二弦第五品 E ，
if I want to slide up to it,
如果我想滑动到它，
I just start somewhere beneath it,
我从它下面的某个地方开始，
let's say a half a step,
比如半步，
and I slide into it,
然后我滑动到它，
so I'm actually playing it on the fourth fret
所以是在第四品弹奏，
and then I keep the pressure on this finger
然后我保持对这个手指的压力，
and slide up to the fifth fret.
滑动到第五品。
you gotta do it fairly quickly,
你需要做得快一点，
to make it work out.
让它工作。
Let's do exercise number one, for slides,
我们来做滑弦的第一个练习，
okay, without the slide, the [line] would go like this,
好的，没有滑弦，是这样的，
if I do the slide, turns out to be this,
如果我做滑弦，是这样的，
do you hear how that slide change the sound of it,
你听到滑弦是怎么改变声音的吗，
do one more time, with the slide.
再来一次，使用滑弦。
One of my favorite slide licks is
我最喜欢的滑弦之一是，
and you can do it in any key
你可以用任何调来做，
I'm going to start, we're going to do it in C
我要从 C 开始，
and then I'll show it on the six string, we're going F too,
然后我会在第六弦上，使用 F ，
go into it in C,
我们要用 C 来做，
and the lick starts out like this,
片段开始像这样，
if I were to just play it without the slides it be C,
如果我只是弹奏它，没有使用滑弦，就是 C ，
okay, now if I slide into that, E right here,
现在如果滑动到它，在这里的 E ，
how I do that is,
我该怎么做，
I put my third finger on this D
我把无名指放在这个 D 上，
and I slide up now to this G,
然后滑动到这个 G ，
so let's just do the first half,
我们来做前半部分，
hear how that's gonna sound,
听听这会是什么声音，
and I do the same thing,
我做同样的事情，
putting my third finger on the G,
把我的无名指放在 G 上，
so I've got my hand actually in the wrong position,
所以我的手放在了错误的位置，
then I slide up to that A
然后我滑到那个 A ，
and hit that first finger C.
然后点击食指 C 。
So let's do it together slowly,
所以让我们一起慢慢地做，
[] your hand back,
[]你的手回来，
one more time.
再来一次。
Okay, and if I was playing that in tempo would sound like this,
好的，如果我在节奏中弹奏，听起来像这样，
now I can actually keep going,
现在我可以继续，
just take it up to take all those things up in octave,
把所有的东西都升高八度，
if I was going down and it would be a little trickier,
如果我往下走，会有点棘手，
we can only do it on the E go down to D.
我们只能从 E 到 D 。
Okay, now that's it in C,
好的，这是在 C 中，
if I wanted to do an f with a six string root,
如果我想用第六弦来做 F ，
it's pretty much the same thing,
这几乎是一样的，
we have to just the fingering just a little bit,
我们只需要一点指法，
so an F would be like this,
所以 F 像是这样，
if I want to keep going,
如果我想要继续，
if I can squeeze one more out of it.
如果我能再挤进一个。
Okay.
好的。
It's a good way
这是一个好方法，
to get a really large lick going from low to high notes
使用一个大的片段从低到高的音符，
and you can incorporate that into any key
你可以把它整合到任何音调中，
and you can go all over the neck
你可以通过这个琴颈，
by just using that little pattern,
通过使用这个模式，
one of my favorite slide patterns.
我最喜欢的滑弦模式之一。
Let's go to the next one, bends,
让我们到下一个，推弦，
alright, there's some tech here's all I know about bends,
好的，这是我知道的推弦的一些技术，
you want to do, you can bend a note a half step or a whole step up,
你可以把一个音符推弦升高半音或全音，
let's talk about the proper technique for bends too,
让我们来讨论一下推弦的适当技术，
usually it's involving the third or the fourth finger.
通常涉及到无名指或小拇指。
Okay, so let's say I'm on this D,
好的，假设我在这个 D 上，
the seventh fret with my third finger
我的无名指在第七品上，
and I want to bend that up,
我想把它弯曲起来，
okay, well, here we're going to come across another physical problem for,
好的，在这里，我们会遇到另一个身体问题，
it may take a couple of weeks for you to get a handle on physically,
因为你可能需要几个星期的时间来处理它，
because we've got to strengthen up these fingers,
因为我们必须加强这些手指，
I'm gonna bend using this third finger bend, this D up to an E,
我要用这个无名指弯曲，让 D 上升到 E ，
okay, now I'm not, if I just try it,
好的，我不是，如果我只是试一下，
you may have to bring this,
你可能要把这个拿起来，
remember I told you never to bring your wrist up,
记住我告诉过你永远不要把手腕抬起来，
here's the one case where you can bring your wrist up,
这是一个例子，你可以把手腕抬起来，
get a little bit more pressure there,
稍微用力一点，
bring that thumb over, if you need to,
如果你需要的话，把大拇指举过来，
sometimes if it's hard to bring this note all the way up,
有时如果很难把这个音符举起来，
use these other two fingers behind him to help bring that string up,
用它后面的另外两个手指帮助把琴弦拉起来，
so you put them all three of them down
这样你就把三根手指都放下来，
and now bend that note up.
然后把音符向上弯曲。
That's using our third finger,
那就是用我们的无名指，
if I wanted to do one that would be using my fourth finger,
如果我想用我的小拇指，
maybe I could go this G here
也许我可以在 G 这里，
and I could bend him up,
我可以把他弯曲起来，
now I can bend up just a half step,
现在我可以弯曲半音，
let's go back to my D,
让我们回到 D ，
half step up would be Eb, that's that note,
半音将是 Eb ，那个音符，
or I can do a whole note, a whole step,
或者我可以做一个全音，
that would be a whole step, half step,
这将是全音，半音，
now one of the secrets to bending
推弦的秘诀之一，
and I learned this from Larry Carlton,
我从 Larry Carlton 那里学到的，
one of the greatest guitar players,
他是最伟大的吉他演奏家之一，
that incorporates this style,
融合了这种风格，
he said, that when you bend,
他说，当你推弦时，
bend up to a pitch, don't just bend up somewhere,
推到一个音高，不要只是推到某个地方，
which is what a lot of guitar players do
这是很多吉他演奏者做的，
and they're playing a solo
他们弹奏 solo ，
and they just kind of bend around and bend up,
他们只是推弦，
it's kind of a lazy man's way of doing it,
这是一种懒人的做法，
when you're gonna bend, bend to a pitch,
当你推弦时，推到一个音高，
either a half step up or a whole step up,
无论是半音还是全音，
okay, takes a little bit of a trick,
好的，需要一点技巧，
a little bit of control do that,
一点控制来做到，
and that's the whole issue,
这就是整个问题，
control, don't just kind of bend somewhere, bend to a pitch.
控制，不要只是推弦到某个地方，推到一个音高。
Okay, so we've talked about half step bends,
好的，我们已经讨论了半音推弦，
we've talked about whole step bends,
我们已经讨论了全音推弦，
now let's incorporate those into our pentatonic scale.
现在让我们把它们合并到我们的五声音阶中。
Okay, so here's our A minor pentatonic,
好的，这是我们的 A 小调五声音阶，
first form here that we've used some often,
我们经常使用的第一种形式，
what notes are good to bend in that,
什么音符方便推弦，
well, you don't want to bend on these low notes,
好的，你不想在这些低音上推弦，
it just gets a little bit, just too low doesn't sound real good,
它有点，音高太低，不会好听，
here's the first one that starts being good to bend,
这是第一个开始很好推弦的，
I can bend this one a half step,
我可以推弦半音，
which would get me to the []
这会让我达到[]，
or I can bend up a whole step,
或者我可以推弦全音，
which would get me to the whole a [] [],
这将把我带到全[]，
okay, so that note is good to bend,
所以这个音符很好地推弦，
either half step or whole step,
无论是半音还是全音，
this G, I can bend it up a whole step and it sounds great,
这个 G ，我可以把它推弦全音，听起来很棒，
okay, I don't want to bend up just a half step,
好的，我不想推弦半音，
that doesn't sound too good to get out of the key,
这听起来不太好，有点跑调，
note also that I can bend is this pinky right here,
我也可以推弦的音符是这里的小拇指，
now you got to kind of play with your fingers on that string,
现在你可以用你的手指在那根弦上弹奏，
what do you do with your fingernails
你用你的指甲做什么，
and where does the actual strings that you're coming into,
你要把弦放到哪里，
where do they go,
它们去哪里，
do they go, if you can,
如果你可以，
if you get your fingernails down close enough to the fret board,
如果你的指甲离指板足够近，
you can push those other strings up,
你可以把其他的弦向上推，
actually over your nail,
在你的指甲上面，
and that's one way to do it,
这是实现这个目标的一种方法，
if you've got, if you go out completely another direction
如果你走一个完全不同的方向，
and go at a real flat,
在一个降音上，
you just push all those other strings up underneath,
你只需要把所有其他的弦往上推，
there's two ways you need to do it,
你需要用两种方法来做，
you need to figure out which way works best for you,
你需要找出哪种方法对你最有效，
okay so that notes that we can bend a pentatonic scale
所以我们在五声音阶中推弦的音符是，
are this one, this one and this one
这个，这个和这个，
in that first pentatonic form.
在第一个五声音阶形式中。
Okay, the other forms would have different notes that those can bend too,
其他形式会有不同的音符可以推弦，
but they would be the same equivalent pitches,
但它们将是相同的音高，
the D G and the and C, are the ones that we can use,
D G 和 C 是我们可以使用的，
one of the best exercises, you can use to strengthen your hand
你可以用来加强你的手最好的练习之一，
and all these bends involve strengthening your hands, strengthening these fingers,
所有这些推弦涉及加强你的手，加强这些手指，
you don't get it the first time,
一开始你没有得到，
some of you might, if you have strong hands,
你们中的一些人第一次可能会，如果你有强大的手，
but the other ones will have to work on a little bit
但其他人必须努力一点，
has to do with string, how thick your strings are,
与弦有关，你的弦有多粗，
how strong your hand is, that sort of stuff,
你的手有多强，这类的东西，
a great exercise that Larry Carlton uses is
Larry Carlton 使用的一种很好的练习是，
doing a major scale with bends,
使用推弦来做一个大调音阶，
I'm going to play through solely
我会单独弹奏，
and then we'll talk about him,
然后我们会讨论它，
C D and then we bend up to this E,
C D ，然后我们推弦到这个 E ，
then I have to stick my first finger up here that F, G bend up to the A,
然后我把食指放到 F ， G 推弦到 A ，
we're going to pitch, B C,
我们到音高 B C ，
I did it again, C D E,
我再做一次， C D E ，
putting in a major scale format is really easy to hear,
很容易听到大音阶的格式，
when you're not quite at it,
当你不是很擅长的时候，
okay, going down, it's a little bit different
好的，向下有点不同，
here your first finger is here, C
你的食指在 C 这里，
and I'm gonna bend up to this B from this A,
我将从这个 A 推弦到这个 B ，
can bend up from this D,
可以从这个 D 向上推弦，
so let's go down one more time,
让我们再来一次，
C, then from the A to the B,
C ，然后 A 到 B ，
A G F, bend up to the E,
A G F ，推弦到 E ，
D C,
D C ，
if I put it in context,
如果我把它放在上下文中，
it would be a good exercise to get your hands strong enough,
这将是一个很好的练习，让你的手足够强壮，
to do the bends that you need
来做你需要的推弦，
and incorporate those into your play.
并把它们整合到你的演奏中。
Next thing we want to talk about is hammer-ons,
下一件事我们想讨论的是击弦，
okay, what's a hammer-on,
好的，什么是击弦，
well, it's not a shark,
它不是鲨鱼，
what a hammer-on, that's a hammerhead,
这是 hammer-on ，那是 hammerhead （锤头鲨），
hammer-on is, if I'm using that same form,
击弦，如果我使用同样的形式，
I'm going to take my,
我将使用我的，
let's say I'm starting on this E,
假设我从这个 E 开始，
and I'm going to hammer-on to this G,
我要击弦这个 G ，
what is involved practically is,
实际上涉及的是，
I'm just going to take this pinky G
我要拿着这个小拇指 G ，
and whack my pinky down as hard as I can,
尽我所能地击打我的小拇指，
I'm not gonna, I only play the E,
我不会，我只会弹奏 E ，
I don't pick the G,
我不会选择 G ，
I just force my pinky down so strong,
我只是用小拇指下沉的力度很大，
that it actually sounds out the G,
使 G 发声，
think of it like a hammer-on a piano,
想象是敲击钢琴，
if you ever looked inside a piano,
如果你看过钢琴的内部，
there's a hammer that's actually hitting those strings,
有一个锤子上在敲击那些琴弦，
and that's what you're G fingers doing,
这就是你的手指在 G 所做的，
if I do it on A to a C.
如果我做 A 到 C 。
Okay, now I can do this,
好的，我可以做这个，
with first to second finger, first to third finger, first to fourth finger.
用食指到中指，食指到无名指，食指到小拇指。
So let's look at our hammer-on exercise,
让我们看看击弦练习，
the first one goes from like E to F,
第一个从 E 到 F ，
trying to get that second note to sound out,
试着让第二个音符发声，
keep that pressure on you,
保持你的压力，
really have to whack it against that fret board,
必须敲击那个指板，
let's go from E F# or one to three,
让我们从 E 到 F# 或 1 到 3 ，
what about E to G, one to four.
E 到 G 怎么样， 1 到 4 。
Okay, try it on different strings,
好的，在不同的琴弦上试一试，
try it on different places on the fret board,
在琴板上的不同位置试一试，
takes a little bit of muscle in that pinky
小拇指需要一点肌肉，
to get to hammer-on strong enough,
才能击弦得足够有力，
but that's what you're going for,
但这就是你想要的，
you want both notes to actually sound pretty similar.
你想让两个音符听起来非常相似。
Now let's talk about the flip side of hammer-ons, which is pull-offs,
现在让我们来谈谈击弦的另一面，也就是勾弦，
pull-offs,
勾弦，
let's say I'm going from this G
比如，我从这个 G 开始，
and I want to get back to this E
我想回到这个 E ，
without picking the note,
不拨动音符，
instead of picking it like that,
不是像这样，
I have my finger on this G
我把手指放在这个 G 上，
and I'm gonna pull down,
我会向下拉，
I got a lot of pressure on this E
我对这个 E 有很大的压力，
and I pull down and release that string.
我向下拉，然后松开那根弦。
So I'm doing two things,
所以我在做两件事，
not only am I pulling down with this string,
我不仅把这根弦往下拉，
I'm also giving counter pressure with this finger,
我还用这根手指反压，
not only I'm pulling down with this finger,
不仅我用这根手指往下拉，
but I'm giving counter pressure with this finger,
我用这根手指反压，
so one finger's going down, one finger's going up,
所以一根手指向下，一根手指向上，
I do with my third finger,
我用我的无名指练习，
practice it with your second finger, third finger, fourth finger,
用你的中指练习，无名指，小拇指，
now I can combine those with a hammer-on,
我可以把它们和击弦结合起来，
I hammer-on one way and then pull-off the other,
我击弦一个，然后勾弦另一个，
I'm only actually hitting one note with my pick
我只用拨片敲击一个音符，
and the rest of it, my fingers are doing.
其余的是我的手指做的。
Okay, so incorporating hammer-ons and pull-offs into your playing,
所以把击弦和勾弦结合到你的演奏中，
now hammer-on,
现在，击弦，
let's talk about one specific technique,
让我们来谈谈一种具体的技巧，
that we need to work on with a hammer-ons and pull-offs，
我们需要用击弦和勾弦来完成，
that would be the Eddie Van Halen type of tapping,
那就是 Eddie Van Halen 式点弦，
okay, bunch of different skills involved with this one,
好的，这个有很多不同的技巧，
let me do it without distortion first,
让我先做一个没有失真的，
then I'll do it with distortion,
然后再做一个有失真的，
let's say I'm going between this E and this G,
假设我在这个 E 和 G 之间，
and I'm also gonna come over here with my first finger and hit this A,
我也会用我的食指到这里，点击这个 A ，
so I got three things going, I got the E, G, A,
所以我有三件事，我得到了 E G A ，
now, I'm not Eddie Van Halen,
我不是 Eddie Van Halen ，
but basically here's the deal on that concept,
但基本上是这样的概念，
you kind of starts the note,
你开始这个音符，
pull-off,
勾弦，
with this finger, I'm actually kind of tugging down a little bit of,
用这根手指开始拉，
I'm kind of doing pull-off with my other finger,
我用我的另一根手指勾弦，
okay, that's basically it,
好的，基本上就是这样，
now gets infinitely more complex than that,
比这个要复杂的多，
but that's basically the technique that's being used,
但基本上这就是使用的技术，
throw a little distortion, little delay, crank it up,
加入一点失真，一点延迟，调高音量，
sound rock and roll with it,
使它听起来摇滚，
that's basically what that technique is.
这就是这个技术。
Now, another thing,
现在，还有一件事，
if I want to incorporate hammer-ons and pull-offs into my pentatonic scale,
如果我想把击弦和勾弦结合到我的五声音阶中，
well, I can go something like this,
我可以这样做，
I'm actually hitting the first one of each pair,
我敲击每一对中的第一个，
sometimes hammer-ons and pull-offs are a great way to get a lot of speed
有时候击弦和勾弦是提高速度的一种很好的方式，
without actually having to pick it all,
完全不需要拨动它，
sounds really impressive,
听起来很令人印象深刻，
sounds like I'm going really fast,
听起来像我真的很快，
actually I'm, I guess my fingers on this hand are doing all the work,
实际上我这只手的手指在做所有的工作，
but not this hand,
而不是这只手，
I'm using all hammer-ons and pull-offs,
我所有都使用击弦和勾弦，
so practice doing scales practice, doing our pentatonic scales
所以练习做音阶练习，做五声音阶联系，
with those and hammer-on, hammering-on and pulling them off.
使用击弦和勾弦。
Okay, okay, the next thing I want to talk about is muting with our palm,
好的，接下来我想谈的是用我们的手掌闷音，
very common technique,
很常见的技巧，
I did a little bit, when we, when we had our welcome part little bit earlier,
我在前面的欢迎部分使用了一些，
and that was the thing that I did, using palm muting,
这就是我所做的，使用手掌闷音，
I'm taking this part of the fleshy part of my palm on my right hand,
我把右手手掌的这一肉质部分，
putting it right at the bridge down here,
把它放在下面的琴桥上，
and then I'm playing a note,
然后我演奏一个音符，
let's say I'm playing an A here, at the seventh fret,
比如我弹奏一个第七品的 A ，
okay, now if I put it too far back,
如果我把它放得太远，
it just sounds like a regular string,
它听起来就像是一根普通的弦，
but put it too far up,
但放得太高了，
it kind of gets this funny sounds,
听起来有点滑稽，
it takes a little while to figure out getting just the sweet spot,
需要一段时间才能弄清楚，找到甜区，
where you can hear where it's supposed to be,
在哪里可以听到想要的，
I can do my major pentatonic minor pentatonic, excuse me,
我可以做我的大调五声音阶，抱歉，小调五声音阶，
it lends itself a little bit easier doing all down strokes rather than down and up,
它让自己更容易做所有的下而不是下上，
it's hard to do,
很难做到，
I guess you can do ups,
我想你可以做上，
but it lends itself a bit better doing down strokes on that,
但它在下上做得更好，
so I'm practicing, practice on that,
所以我在练习，
you get this hand straight,
你把这只手放直，
put it on that bridge, a little bit up from bridge.
把它放在琴桥上，琴桥上稍微高一点。
Okay, now if I'm in let's say Am, Am chord,
好的，如果我在 Am 和弦上，
remember our triads is built up of an A C and E,
记得我们的三和弦是由 A C 和 E 组成的，
okay, if I'm in Am7 be A C E and G,
如果我是 Am7 ，将是 A C E G ，
now I can take,
现在，我可以，
I don't want to play an Am7 the whole time,
我不想全部弹奏 Am7 ，
if I want to have a [],
如果我想要 [] ，
well that's not very interesting, if I'm doing a rhythm accompaniment with it,
这并不是很有趣，如果我用它做节奏伴奏，
so a lot of times, I can just take certain notes of that chord,
所以很多时候我可以用它来做某些和弦的音符，
do a little palm muting with it
做一些手掌闷音，
and I end up making some music with it.
用它来做一段音乐。
Okay, take a listen to [] here,
好的，听一下这一段，
I'm just using the A,
我只是用 A ，
I'm using G and A,
我使用 G 和 A ，
then I throw the C and E in there too,
我把 C 和 E 也加进去，
one of the most helpful techniques I've ever learned is that palm muting,
我学过的最有用的技巧之一就是手掌闷音，
folks, some folks will put up a song,
有些人会放一首歌，
I don't know whether, I don't know anything,
我不知道任何东西，
what the chord changes are anything,
和弦变化是什么，
I'm supposed to play something fabulous,
我应该演奏一些很棒的东西，
you just take whatever key you're in,
你只要拿你所在的调，
I play the root of that key
我演奏那个调的根音，
and I've got it,
我就得到了，
let's say, in C,
假设在 C 中，
I don't know what the chord changes are,
我不知道和弦变化是什么，
I don't know anything,
我什么都不知道，
I just I just vamp on that C
我只是在那个 C 上弹奏，
and it sounds hip,
它听起来很时髦，
through a couple notes around it,
通过几个音符在它周围，
and yeah you can still work,
是的，你仍然可以工作，
you've got a good funky guitar part that you can play,
你有一个很好的时髦的吉他部分，
you're not just hammering out the chords
你不只是敲击和弦，
which is what every other guitar player would do,
像其他吉他演奏者那样，
you've got something unique
你有一些独特的东西，
and all of this is you're just taking the root of the chord or the fifth sometimes,
所有这一切就是你只取和弦的根音，或者第五音，
do a little palm muting,
做手掌闷音，
come up with a little rhythm with it
用它来产生一点节奏，
and that's all that is.
就是这样。
Okay, another technique I want to show you is
好的，我想告诉你的另一种技巧是，
picking, while you're picking, putting my second finger the nail, just down on the string,
当你拨弦时，把中指指甲靠在弦上，
just setting it on the string, while I'm playing,
当我弹奏时，把它靠在弦上，
it gets this little bit of a harmonic happening
它会发生一点泛音，
and it's real, real cool, real common sound,
这是非常酷的，非常普通的声音，
so if I'm playing, let's say a C major scale,
所以如果我弹奏的是 C 大调音阶，
now I'm just gonna set my second finger nail on top of those strings as,
现在我会把我的中指指甲放在那些弦的上面，
you hear how it doesn't come out perfect all the time,
你会听到它并不总是完美的，
but sometimes it gets a [] harmonic way at top,
但有时它会发出尖叫声，
okay, throw a little distortion on that,
好的，加一点失真，
hear that harmonic way up there,
听到这里的泛音，
that's all coming from using that second finger nail on that,
这都是因为用中指指甲在上面，
it takes a little practice to get it down,
掌握它需要一点练习，
but once you get it,
但一旦你学会了，
it's a real [] effect,
这是一个[]效果，
that you can put into your playing.
你可以把它放到你的演奏中。
Last thing I want to talk about is octaves,
最后我想说的是八度，
let's say I'm playing, a guy puts up a song
假设我在演奏一首歌，
and I'm supposed to sound jazzy,
我应该听起来很爵士，
okay, well I can play in octaves,
好的，我可以用八度演奏，
now octaves in our music notation,
八度，在我们的乐谱中，
if I'm playing a C,
如果我演奏的是 C ，
that would be a low C and a high C, play at the same time,
那将是低音 C 和高音 C 同时演奏，
okay, how it fingers well best,
好的，手指如何，
how it fingers best on guitar,
手指如何在吉他上，
so if I use one and three,
所以如果我使用食指和无名指，
now, how do I play those,
现在，我如何弹奏，
because I've got a string in between,
因为我有一根弦在中间，
without getting that string to sound,
不能让那根弦发声，
well, actually got my, I play it kind of sloppy
我演奏得有点马虎，
and I put my first finger down on that middle string,
我把我的食指靠在中间的那根弦上，
so actually what you're hearing is,
所以实际上你听到的是，
you're hearing that dead string in between them,
你听到它们之间的那根死弦，
when I play it all together,
当我一起演奏它时，
but it doesn't come out,
但它没有出来，
I can do it on the six string,
我可以在第六弦上弹奏，
I can use one four perhaps,
我可能可以使用食指和小拇指，
one four,
食指和小拇指，
okay, when I go down to the next set of strings, the fourth and second,
当我到下一组弦时，第四弦和第二弦，
I've got to open up, use only one four,
我必须打开，只能使用食指和小拇指，
because that's how the guitar is tuned,
因为吉他是这样调音的，
you end up with a wider stretch,
你需要更宽的拉伸，
same thing for the next string,
同样的东西对于下一根弦，
octaves takes a little bit practicing to get it,
八度需要一些练习，
what you get, if I want to sound jazzy,
如果我想听起来很爵士，
I just do octaves like that,
我做这样的八度，
now there's a great jazz guitarist Wes Montgomery,
有一位伟大的爵士乐吉他手 Wes Montgomery ，
he didn't use a pick, he used his thumb for these octaves,
他没有使用拨片，他用他的拇指做这些八度音阶，
gets even a sweeter sound,
得到了更甜美的声音，
you can see how [] sound gets,
你可以看到[]声音是如何做到的，
okay, now if I want to fake that sound,
如果我想伪造那个声音，
sometimes I can just flick my third finger instead of picking,
有时我可以只弹我的无名指而不是拨片，
I'm using my third finger
我使用我的无名指，
and just kind of whacking the back of my third finger there,
然后用我的无名指敲击，
Jazz octaves.
爵士八度。
Okay, now let's take a look at some more techniques,
好的，现在让我们看看更多的技巧，
that use your guitar and your instrument for actually creating some different techniques.
使用你的吉他和你的乐器来创造一些不同的技巧。
Okay, now we're gonna talk about using our guitar instrument
好的，现在我们将讨论如何使用我们的吉他乐器，
and we're giving some different techniques out of that,
我们将给出一些不同的技巧，
first thing to talk about is using a capo,
首先要讨论的是使用变调夹，
now here's a capo,
这是变调夹，
what, what is involved in a little metal thing,
一个小小的金属东西，
probably cost you four or five bucks down at the music store,
可能在音乐商店要花你四五美元，
okay, pretty strong
好的，相当有力，
and you put it over the neck of your guitar,
你把它夹在你的吉他琴颈上，
like I could put the third fret.
比如我可以把它夹在第三品。
Now what's the capo used for,
变调夹是做什么的，
well, here's a couple things,
好的，这里有几件事，
the first thing, it's used for,
它用来做的第一件事是，
if I want to just do simple chord progressions
如果我想做简单的和弦进程，
and I only know G Cs and Ds
我只知道 G C 和 D ，
and I only know open chords,
我只知道开放和弦，
but I want to be able to use my open chords in a song,
但我希望能够在一首歌中使用我的开放和弦，
that does not is not an open chord key like G C or D,
而它不是像 G C 或 D 这样的开放和弦的调，
let's say the song is in Eb or something different like that,
让我们假设这首歌是 Eb 调的，或者类似的，
well, no problem,
好的，没问题，
you find, let's say the chords are D G and A,
假设和弦是 D G 和 A ，
but they want to do it,
但他们想要这样做，
they want to take it up the key and do it in Eb,
他们想要升调，在 Eb 调中弹，
well, no problem,
好的，没问题，
the distance between d and Eb,
D 和 Eb 之间的距离，
the key that I know my chords in and Eb where we're going is one half step,
我知道和弦的调和我们要去的 Eb 距离是半音，
which is one frets worth on the guitar,
这是吉他上的一品，
so I put my capo at the first fret
所以我把变调夹放在第一品，
and now I've got my D chord, G chord, A chord,
现在我有 D 和弦， G 和弦， A 和弦，
but now I can play it in a different key,
但现在我可以用不同的调弹奏，
so I'm playing a D,
所以我弹奏的是 D ，
but it's actually sounding as an Eb,
但它听起来是 Eb ，
see that change the sound of a guitar,
看到它是如何改变吉他声音的吗，
I can go even more than that,
我可以做得更多，
let's say I wanted to do my D chord,
比如，我想要做我的 D 和弦，
but we're going to use it in the key of G,
但我们要用它在 G 调，
well, the distance for [] D and a G is a fourth,
好的， D 和 G 的距离是四个，
well, that is five frets worth on a guitar,
好的，这相当于吉他上的五品，
so I would have to put it at,
所以我必须把它放在，
let's see what, the sixth fret, sixth fret [], sixth frets [],
让我们看看，第六品，
sorry, I was right, the first time, fifth fret.
抱歉，我第一次是对的，第五品。
Capos were great,
变调夹很好，
but after I get out too far,
但在我离开太远之后，
it's kind of hard for,
它有点困难，
it's just too hard and too small for fingers to get in there,
对于手指来说太小，很难到那里，
so they work best down here,
所以它们在这里工作得最好，
now you see the mental calculations I had to go through
你看到我不得不进行心算，
in order to find out where to place the capo,
为了找出变调夹放在哪里，
what's involved is
这里涉及的是，
you take the key that you're doing the chords in D G C whatever
你用来做和弦的调， D G C 等，
and the key that you're going to,
你要去的调，
you want to use those chords in,
你想要用到的调，
let's say I wanted to use the Eb,
比如，我想使用 Eb ，
okay, and I'm starting on a D,
好的，我从 D 开始，
I count up one, the distance between D and Eb is one half step,
我加一， D 和 Eb 之间的距离是半音，
which is one frets worth on the guitar,
相当于吉他上的一品，
so I put it at the first fret,
所以我把它放在第一品上，
If I were going from D to F,
如果我从 D 到 F ，
you have to count half steps,
你必须数半音，
D to Eb, Eb to E, E to F,
D 到 Eb ， Eb 到 E ， E 到 F ，
that's three steps,
这是三步，
so I would put it at the third fret, one two three.
所以我会把它放在第三品上，一二三。
Okay, then I wanna talk about is harmonics,
好的，然后我想说的是泛音，
well, what are harmonics,
好的，什么是泛音，
well, there's a couple of things,
好的，有几个事情。
when I play stuff like,
当我演奏像这样的东西时，
sorry.
抱歉。
This is a string,
这是一根弦，
the exact midway point of that string is at the twelfth fret,
那根弦的准确的中点是在第十二品，
if I just barely touch that twelfth fret,
如果我只是勉强接触到第十二品，
not fret it, just barely touch exactly over the fret,
不是品，它只是勉强接触到品丝，
not behind the fret, like we have been doing, when we've actually figured that,
而不是像我们一直在做的那样，在品丝后面，
if I just barely touched over the fret,
如果我仅仅只是触摸品丝，
can get this bell like sound,
就可以得到像铃声一样的声音，
which is the exact midway point of the string
这是在弦上的确切中点，
in physical sciences called a node, in music, it's called a harmonic.
在物理学中称为节点，在音乐中称为泛音。
There's one at the twelfth fret,
有一个在第十二品，
now it doesn't work,
现在它不起作用了，
if I'm at the eleventh fret, doesn't work,
如果我在第十一品，不起作用，
thirteen fret, doesn't work,
第十三品，不起作用，
it's very precise, twelve fret, where you get them.
它非常精确，第十二品，你可以得到它们。
I can also get at the seventh fret,
我也可以在第七品得到，
I can also get at the fifth fret,
我也可以在第五品得到，
after that it gets pretty hard to get them.
在它之后，很难得到它们。
So the ones that you mainly use this one is the strongest,
所以你主要使用的这个是最强的，
this is the next strongest,
这个是次强的，
this one is the next strongest, next weak, excuse me.
这个是次强的，抱歉，次弱的。
Sometimes I can incorporate that into my playing,
有时候我可以把它融入我的演奏中，
if I'm playing let's see a G chord,
如果我在弹奏比如 G 和弦，
that has open D, open G, open B,
它有开放 D ，开放 G ，开放 B ，
I can hit that right there,
我可以在那里弹奏，
that would be a D triad,
这是一个 D 三和弦，
that would be a G triad,
这是一个 G 三和弦，
that harmonics at work.
这是泛音的工作方式。
I also with a little bit of effort
再加上一点努力，
can do what's called false harmonics,
我也可以做所谓的伪和弦，
okay, so let's say I do a barre chord,
好的，假设我做一个横按和弦，
well, if I just play an octave up from each of these strings,
如果我从每根弦上拉一个八度，
I can get another harmonic,
我就能得到另一个泛音，
with using my first finger,
使用我的食指，
I'm gonna pluck with my thumb,
我要用我的拇指拔，
and barely touch the string with my first finger
用我的食指几乎不碰琴弦，
exactly an octave up from where I'm fingering,
正好离我手指的位置高一个八度，
so if my barre is here,
所以如果我的横按在这里，
on this F,
在这个 F 上，
then I go up to this F here,
然后我走到这个 F ，
barely touch it and pluck it
几乎不碰它，然后拔动它，
and I get the harmonic,
我得到了泛音，
then, if I just kind of outline the chord,
然后，如果我只是勾勒出和弦，
C F A C F,
C F A C F ，
I have to kind of outline the chord,
我必须勾勒出和弦，
I can get some false harmonics here,
我可以在这里得到一些虚假的泛音，
I can do melodies with them,
我可以用它来做旋律，
I think if I play.
我想如果我弹奏。
Okay, if I wanted to do let's say a little scale,
好的，如果我想做音阶，
okay, I'm doing this false harmonic,
好的，我在做这个假泛音，
I'm pulling off this note right there.
我在这里弹出这个音符。
So I'm combining a whole bunch of different things,
所以我结合了很多不同的东西，
you just have to be real accurate where those harmonics are at,
你只需要非常准确地知道那些泛音在哪里，
anyway, those are some different techniques that you can use,
这些是一些不同的技巧，
when playing to throw some little spice into your playing.
你可以在演奏时，增加一点额外的音色。
Let's talk about our assignment for this this week,
让我们来谈谈本周的作业，
your assignment for this session is
你们这节课的作业是，
I want you to practice the bending exercises that we have in your book,
我想让你们练习书中的推弦练习，
practice bending controlled into a pitch,
练习推弦控制成音高，
remember Larry Carlton's thing,
记得 Larry Carlton 的事情，
we don't just bend up, we bend to a pitch,
我们不只是推弦，我们推弦到一个音高，
use that major scale exercise
使用大调音阶练习，
to help you get some strength in your hand
帮助你在手中获得力量
to do those bends on that major scale.
来做这些推弦在大调音阶中。
Next thing in what you do is the slide riff exercise, that we talked about,
你接下来要做的就是我们说过的滑弦片段练习，
do it on the sixth string,
在第六弦上做，
okay, on the fifth string,
好的，在第五弦上做，
practicing in different keys and different places on the neck,
在不同的调和琴颈不同的地方练习，
you can incorporate that into your toolkit of playing,
你可以把它整合到你的演奏工具包中，
okay, whip those out, when you need to do a solo.
好的，当你需要 solo 的时候，把它们拿出来。
Practice doing your pentatonic scales
练习你的五音音阶，
using the palm muting that we talked about,
使用我们讨论过的手掌闷音，
[] for a good clear tone,
得到一个好的清晰的音调，
also work on those jazz octaves,
也在爵士乐的八度上起作用，
I give up my pick, my thumb,
我放下拨片，使用大拇指，
back my third finger, slides,
回到我的无名指，滑弦，
all these little things make your playing interesting and unique.
所有这些小东西都让你的演奏有趣和独特。
So, we'll go ahead and see you next time.
所以我们继续，下次再见。
Okay, first thing we're gonna do in our workshop today is bends,
好的，我们今天在 workshop 要做的第一件事是推弦，
remember our good proper technique for bends,
记住我们很好的推弦技巧，
if I want to bend up,
如果我想推弦，
I can use these other fingers behind this,
我可以用这个后面的其他手指，
third finger, fourth finger to help that string get up.
无名指，小拇指来帮助推弦。
Okay, in order to strengthen that finger,
好的，为了加强那个手指，
we're going to do a simple exercise,
我们要做一个简单的练习，
we're going to go from the D to an E, bend up to an Eb, just a half step.
我们要从 D 到 E ，推弦到 Eb ，只有半音。
Okay, nice and slow, ready go,
好的，慢慢来，准备，开始，
D Eb,
D Eb ，
D Eb.
D Eb 。
Now let's go up to a D to an E,
现在让我们从 D 到 E ，
we're gonna bend it up a whole step,
我们要把它推弦一个全音，
D E,
E E ，
D E.
D E 。
Now let's do it with our fourth finger,
现在让我们用小拇指来做，
so let's go to this G here,
所以我们到这个 G ，
we're going to take him up a half step and then a whole step,
我们要让他向上半音，然后全音，
half step first,
首先是半音，
ready go, G,
准备，开始， G ，
let's do a whole step,
我们来做一个全音，
remember your pitch that you're going for.
记住你的音高到哪里。
Okay, practice those in different keys and different places on the neck,
好的，在不同的调和琴颈上的不同位置练习，
let's do another place,
让我们做另一个位置，
let's do it, let's begin from this G,
让我们从这个 G 开始，
up to a half step and then a whole step up to A,
上升半音，然后全音到 A ，
so we go to to an Ab first
所以我们先到 Ab ，
or this F, go F to F#,
或者这个 F ， F 到 F# ，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
whole step, F to G.
全音，从 F 到 G 。
Remember a major scale exercise, C D E F G A B C,
记得一个大调音阶练习， C D E F G A B C ，
let's practice it,
让我们练习一下，
ready go,
准备，开始，
C D up to E,
C D ，上升到 E ，
let's go back down,
让我们向下，
C and after the B,
C ，然后是 B ，
A G F E D C,
A G F E D C ，
do it again.
再来一次。
Do it in another place,
在另一个地方做它，
let's do it on F,
让我们在 F 上做，
okay, here's an F, ready, go,
好的，这里是 F ，准备，开始，
don't let yourself be sloppy with all this,
不要让自己在做这个的时候马虎，
do quarter notes.
做四分音符。
Great, let's talk about hammer-ons and pull-offs,
好的，我们来讨论击弦和勾弦，
remember good technique for those when you're hammer-on these notes,
记得当你击弦时的好的技巧，
really whack that fourth finger, third finger, second finger,
真的敲击无名指，中指，食指，
you've got to hit it hard on there,
你必须用力敲击那里，
so this first finger has to be stable
所以食指必须保持稳定，
and then you're really hitting that second finger down,
然后你向下敲击中指，
let's do some hammer-on exercises.
让我们做一些击弦练习。
Okay, we're gonna go, from the, on the fifth position, fifth fret,
好的，我们要，在第五把位，在第五品，
we go for our first or second finger,
我们开始练习食指和中指，
practice that first.
先练习这个。
Let's practice going from one to three,
让我们练习从 1 到 3 ，
let's go for maybe the C to the D here,
让我们从 C 到 D ，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
good clear notes,
很清晰的音符，
let's go from one to four,
让我们从 1 到 4 ，
maybe from this A to the C,
也许从这个 A 到 C ，
really hold it hard.
真的要抓紧。
Great, now let's do some pull-off exercises,
好的，现在让我们做一些勾弦练习，
we're gonna go from four to three,
我们将从四到三，
four to two, four to one.
四到二，四到一。
Okay, starting on this C,
好的，从这个 C 开始，
pinky, reddy go,
小拇指，准备，开始，
then,
然后，
one more time,
再来一次，
a little bit faster.
稍微快一点。
Great, okay, now let's talk over the tapping exercise,
好的，现在我们来讨论一下敲击练习，
we're starting to E, gonna hammer up to this G,
我们从 E 开始，敲击这个 G ，
do a little hammer-on pull-off there,
在这里做击弦勾弦，
then we come up with our first finger hit this A,
然后用我们的食指敲击这个 A ，
and pull-off to that E,
然后勾弦 E ，
see how that works,
看到这是怎么回事，
so going slow a little bit.
所以稍微慢一点。
Okay, let's try one more time,
好的，让我们再试一次，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
now let's put a bunch of them together in a row,
现在我们把它们放在一起，
keep that first finger nice and steady,
保持食指的柔和稳定，
let's speed it up a bit,
让我们稍微加快速度，
see how that works.
看到这是如何工作的。
Okay, next thing we want to cover is our palm muting exercise,
接下来我们要介绍的是手掌闷音练习，
remember good technique,
记得好的技术，
for this bring that wrist back,
把这个手腕带回来，
so gently set that palm on top of your bridge,
所以轻轻地把手掌放在你的琴桥上，
a little bit forward, a little bit in front of it,
稍微向前一点，前面一点，
takes a while to get the sweet spot on it,
需要一些时间才能达到它的最佳位置，
let's do A minor pentatonic,
让我们来做个 A 小调五声音阶，
first form using this palm muting technique,
第一种形式使用这个手掌闷音的技术，
ready, go,
准备，开始，
let's go back down,
让我们往下，
good strong picking, when you do it,
当你做的时候，有力的拨弦，
let's go up to the second form,
让我们到第二种形式，
we haven't done much for the second form,
我们对第二种形式做的不多，
let's do the same thing in the second form,
让我们在第二种形式做同样的事情，
third form.
第三种形式。
Good, now let's play our A minor [] example for you
好的，现在让我们弹奏 A 小调示例，
and you try and incorporate some of that palm muting technique,
你试着加入一些手掌闷音技术，
like Paul Jackson Jr,
像 Paul Jackson Jr 一样，
Paul Jackson Jr, the great guitar players that uses this technique,
Paul Jackson Jr 是伟大的吉他手使用这个技术，
try and just do a single couple of notes out of the key
只需要做调中的几个音符就可以了，
and see if you can make up a rhythm that works out nicely.
看看你能不能编出一个很好的节奏。
Okay, so let's fire it up,
好的，让我们开始吧，
you don't need do I'm doing, find your own,
你不需要做我做的，找到你自己的，
I'm doing G A, G A, G A, G A.
我在做 G A ， G A ， G A ， G A 。
Great, we're gonna play that example one more time,
好的，我们再来一次这个例子，
this time I want you to use
这次我想让你们用一些
some of the Jazz octaves, that we had talked about,
我们说过的爵士乐八度，
really anything you can play,
你可以演奏任何东西，
anything in a C major scale in octaves
C 大调音阶八度的任何东西，
and it's gonna work,
它会奏效的，
let's practice,
让我们练习一下，
you try different rhythms.
你试着不同的节奏。
Great, lot of these techniques add so much to your playing,
好的，这些技巧给你的演奏增加了很多东西，
so you want to try and use them as much as you can,
所以你想试着尽可能多地使用它们，
play a unique style and a unique voice,
演奏出独特的风格和独特的声音，
keep working at these things,
继续在这些事情上努力，
remember winners do what losers are unwilling to do,
记住成功者做失败者不愿意做的事情，
so you're putting forth the effort to better yourself
所以你正在努力改善自己，
and better your guitar playing
改善你的吉他演奏，
and it's gonna pay off in years to come,
这将在几年后得到回报，
when you're playing,
当你演奏的时候，
we'll see later.
我们稍后再见。